{"questionlist":[
{"cardfront":"Hello my name is Faris",
"cardback":"مرحبا اسمي فارس",
"sound":"audio/My name is Faris.mp3"
},
{"cardfront":"Good morning",
"cardback":"صَبَاحَ الْخَيْرِ"
},
{"cardfront":"Saudi (m/f)",
"cardback":"سَعُودِيٌّ \\ سَعُودِيَّةٌ (سَعُودِيُّونَ \\ سَعُودِيَّاتٌ) \n(m/f)"
},
{"cardfront":"happiness",
"cardback":"سعادة "
},
{"cardfront":"cat",
"cardback":"قط "
},
{"cardfront":"dog",
"cardback":"كلب "
},
{"cardfront":"smile",
"cardback":"يبتسم "
},
{"cardfront":"yes",
"cardback":"نعم"
},
{"cardfront":"maybe",
"cardback":"ربما"
},
{"cardfront":"no",
"cardback":"لا"
},
{"cardfront":"maybe",
"cardback":"ربما"
}
]}